

UDISHI VERMA

- Yagati Nagar, Near Florence Apartments, Kotra, 305001 Ajmer, India
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/udishi-verma-00b8301bb/

PROFILE

A content writer with a strong command over keyword selection for SEO and am fairly equipped with the knowledge of various SEO based tools online. I have worked on CRM platforms like Shopify, which has given me a lot of insight on how marketing works. I am passionate about digital marketing in particular, and hope to expand my knowledge in this domain.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

SHOPIFY CONTENT WRITER AND SEO ANALYST

July 2021 - February 2022

Spike Fitness Z

- Wrote Articles on Fitness Products and Physical Well-being.
- Added **Backlinks** and **Interlinks** to Internal and External Websites.
- Performed Keyword Research for each Article.
- Worked Dedicated under a Team Ensuring Good Quality Content.
- Performed Proof Reading.
- Published Articles on **Shopify**.
- Performed **SEO Analysis** for Maximizing Traffic to Blogs.
- Wrote **YouTube Descriptions** for various products offered.
- Received a *Letter of Recommendation* of for this internship.

CONTENT WRITER AND SOCIAL MEDIA ANALYST Singh John

July 2020 – December 2020

Mumbai

• Wrote Articles on **Social Media Marketing** and **Affiliate Marketing**.

- Gave each article innovative thoughts.
- Performed **Proof Reading** for Quality Standards.
- Worked with MS Office.
- Reviewed Products.
- Backlinks, Keyword Research in Social Media Marketing.
- Received a *Letter of Recommendation* of for this internship.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR'S OF COMMERCE

2019 - 2022

Sophia Girls' College (Autonomous)

Ajmer, India

HIGH SCHOOL

2005 - 2019

Sophia Sr, Sec. School

Ajmer, India



Digital Marketing Training (Internshala Trainings)

Internship and Job Preparation (Internshala Trainings)

Social Media Marketing (Edelytics)

Google Search Certification ☑ (Google Skillshop)

SKILLS

Search Engine Optimization

Keyword Analysis

Blog Writing

Microsoft Excel

Communication Skills

Microsoft Word

Proof Reading

Social Media Management

Digital Marketing

Shopify Blog Writing

PowerPoint Presentations

Team Work



X LETTERS OF RECOMMENDATION

Letter of Recommendation

Singh John

Received LOR for exceptional performance at Singh John.

Letter of Recommendation 🖸

Spike Fitness

Received LOR for good work ethics and exemplary skills at Spike Fitness.

INTERESTS

Poems

Dancing

Yoga

Spirituality

Reading

Popular Mythologies

LANGUAGES

English

Hindi

French